Hi everyone, this is EYA on EYA Censor
Supernatural Bible Changes on YouTube
and I want to share this with you.
This is a article on website news. This
was sent to me by Karen
um
in our community.
Canada's House of Commons passes
anti-Christian bill that would
criminalize quoting the Bible. Of course
this would happen.
And essentially
the majority of Canadian MPs have voted
to pass a liberal bill that will allow
the criminalization of religious
expression and belief when quoting parts
of the Bible
including about homosexuality and
gender.
Scrolling down here
it says
Cook said the bill C-9 was framed as a
law going after hate, but in reality it
is a bill
that religious leaders from various
faith communities
say could lead to hate-related charges
against believers
empowers ideologically driven police
officers and judges to target for the
first time the very word of God
on matters of life, family, and faith.
Well, first of all, we know the Bible is
not the word of God. Jesus Christ is the
word of God and we know that. How do we
know that? Because John 1:1 always told
us, "In the beginning was the word and
the word is with God and the word was
God."
And then also in Revelation 19:13
Jesus Christ is the word of God and the
word of God endures forever.
Our Bibles are under satanic assault and
supernaturally changing. And I've been
covering these changes for the past 10
years on YouTube and I want to go ahead
and say, "Yes, I do think it's
interesting that they don't want us to
be talking about the scripture verses
that now relate to homosexuality and
gender because now the Bible is actually
filled with perverse language.
That's right, because the Bible is being
prepared for the Antichrist and coming
one-world satanic system.
It is the abomination of desolation
standing in the holy place. Stay with
me.
Because I'm actually going to show you
some changes to scripture that relate to
homosexuality and gender.
So, stay with me. Oops.
Sorry, just got a phone call.
But let me go ahead and share a few
things with you. So, this is my my
website bible-changes.com
and I'm going to I'm going to go ahead
and I'm going to show you
um
I'm going to show you what I'm talking
about. So, this is an index that I've
created. I just uploaded more verses on
this page here. We have over 7,000
scripture verses that you can search
related to the Bible changes. And this
is just a snippet, okay? It really is.
But I want to go ahead and show you how
you can use this.
This is found again on my webpage and on
the Let me go back to this.
You go back here and you click on search
KJV index of changes and it will take
you to this page and then it gives you
some information on what's happening and
then you can click here. I did an
update, so it looks a little bit
different than it did yesterday. But
here you can see that you can type in
scripture verses, okay? And you can look
for changes. So, I'm going to go and
show you a few right now. Um what comes
to my mind are um
Let's see, where do I want to go?
There's so many of them, okay? But let
me go ahead and show you this one.
This is actually between um
David and Jonathan. You know that they
were best of friends and they loved each
other in a in a holy way, not in an
impure way.
But now we see in 1 Samuel 20:41 it now
says this, "And as soon as the lad was
gone." Lad is a new word. "David arose
out of a place toward the south and fell
on his face." That's right, he fell on
his face. A lot of people now do that in
scripture.
"He fell on his face to the ground and
he bowed himself three times." Just like
an Islamic prayer would.
This was not in the scriptures before.
It goes on to say, "And they kissed one
another." This is Jonathan. David is now
kissing Jonathan
and they wept one with another until
David exceeded.
Yeah, what does that even mean?
Well, it's implied, is it not? And it's
disgusting.
But this is the type of dark changes
that we're seeing in scripture that
definitely have a a really um
questionable
imagery. No doubt about it. Let me go
ahead and show you another one. Here's
another one.
Stay with me. The word is grinding. So,
now we see in Matthew 24:41
it now says, "Two women shall be
grinding at the mill."
And then in Luke 17:35 it now says, "Two
men Two women shall be grinding
together."
That's right, grinding together. No, it
was two two women in the field, one will
be taken, the other will be left. That's
what it said. Nothing about grinding or
grinding together.
I'm going to show you another one. Stay
with me.
This is important.
Grind.
Here's another one in Judges 16:21. This
is what it says, "But the Philistines
took him and put out his eyes." That's
right, he put out his eyes and brought
him down to Gaza. That's a change, too.
"And bound him with fetters of brass and
he did grind in the prison house."
And then we have in Job 31:10 it says,
"Then let my wife grind unto another and
let others bow down upon her."
>> [snorts]
>> And then it goes on. These are really
nasty changes to scripture.
But there's a homosexual transgender
agenda now in scripture. I'm going to
show you another one. Here's another one
and the word that I'm going to go ahead
and show you is the word paps. Paps is
now in the Bible four times and one is
related to supposedly Jesus in the book
of Revelations 1:13. It now says this,
"And in the midst of seven candlesticks
one likened to the son of man." You
know, kind of sort of maybe.
And son of man used to be It wasn't son
of man. They're changing the deity of
Jesus Christ to just be the son of man
instead of the son of God. They're
taking away the deity of Jesus Christ
with these changes in scripture. But
then it goes on, "Clothed with a garment
down to the foot and girt about the paps
with a golden girdle." So, not only does
he have breasts and if you look this
word up in the Strong's Concordance you
will see it means nipples, women's
nipples.
And then he's wearing a golden girdle.
This would be supposedly what Jesus is
now wearing.
Absolutely blasphemous.
With a homosexual agenda, transgender
agenda.
These are a handful of changes that we
are now seeing in scripture that relate
to homosexuality. Now, let's go ahead
and I'll share this with you. There's so
many, there's so many, but I'm just
showing you a few right now just so you
can understand. Here's another new word
in the Bible, gender. We even have
gender strives in the Bible. 2 Timothy
2:23 says this today, "But foolish and
unlearned questions avoid knowing that
they do gender strives."
That's right, gender strives. And we
have certainly seen gender strives
especially in the last decade or really
the last 6 years
where men like to pretend that they can
become women and women can pretend they
can become men and
and then the insanity of pushing it upon
innocent children.
Much more can be said, but I'm going to
refrain.
But the Bible is now filled with wicked
language and innuendos. And all you need
to do, seriously, is just Well, I'm
actually going to show you. I have
another idea for you. Give me a minute.
I'm going to press the back button.
I want to go ahead and show you on my
website I have a link to books that I've
written and I need to tell you that I
have not reviewed the content of any of
my books and I know that there have been
changes to the scriptures that I have
used cuz I I wrote the books a couple
years ago. But just to let you know, I
have a book right here. Oh, you know
what's interesting? For some reason this
book isn't coming up. Why is that not
coming up here?
Okay, well, I'm going to have to find
out why this that this picture is not
coming up for the abomination of
desolation. But this book right here Oh,
where is it?
How interesting is this? Okay, this book
right here, gaslighting, this book has a
lot of scriptures in it related to the
transgender woke ideology that's now
inserted in the King James Bible.
So
lots of examples of Bible changes. Then
I have um I'm going to show you another
one. Okay, I I don't know where it is
and forgive me, but there was another
book, my second book that I wrote
um
has a list of
>> [clears throat]
>> the Bible changes by um
by groupings, okay? So, we what we see
with the changes to scripture, this is
happening satanically, it's witchcraft.
Is it we see different themes being
embedded into scripture today, whether
it's transgenderism, Mormonism,
Catholicism, New Age um
uh [clears throat] wokeism, right? And
all other types of agendas are being
input Islamic, that's another one, are
being input into the Bible to prepare
the way for the Antichrist.
And it blows my mind, to say the least
that the church is woefully asleep.
The Bible is a literally unrecognizable
to me
because of grammar errors, punctuation
errors, new doctrine, new people, new
words, words omitted, whole new passages
have been rewritten.
I mean, we have out the parable of the
bottles now in the Bible, no longer the
parable of the wineskins.
And then don't even get me started with
Luke 19:27 when it talks about now
slaying your enemy.
And another translation it says to
decapitate your enemies.
Please wake up. That's all I can tell
you. What I implore of you is to search
out the matter, pray and fast and seek
the Lord. Jesus Christ is the King of
kings and Lord of lords. He is the word
of God. He's the alpha and omega, the
beginning and the end.
These changes to scripture are clearly
these lying signs and wonders that we
were always warned about would happen.
And those that do not see the changes
are underneath the strong delusion. And
I do believe it's willful blindness.
Because the Bible always told us
that they were they were given over to
the strong delusion. Why? Because they
did not love the truth. And what is
truth?
But Jesus Christ, the word of God.
Christians have been deceived in
thinking that the Bible is or believing
I should say the Bible is like Jesus.
That the Bible is the word of God.
And so because of that, they're now
woefully blinded.
Please wake up. Search out the matter.
There's not much time. Be strong and
courageous, brothers and sisters. Do not
fear be dismayed for the Lord your God
is with you wherever you go.